It used to be so simple
我曾经以为参透
It was a world I understood
世界没有神秘之处
I didn't know what I didn't know
那时未知都还未显露
And life seemed pretty good
生活安好如初
But now the darkness rises
直到在我的心底
From somewwhere deep inside of me
深处的黑暗汹涌来袭
Her power overtakes me
似要掌控我的身体
Can I keep this midnight from getting free?
我能否 在黑暗保持自己？
If I can stay with the light
若我能随光而来
I know I'll be free
就能自由逃离
And I can start to be whole
能让我自己完整
I can start to be me
能开始做自己
But instead I am struggling
但我仍因为所见
With all that I see
而挣扎不息
And these friends
朋友们
Mustn't see the midnight in me!
不能见我心中魔女！
The midnight in me!
那心中魔女！
They mustn't see the midnight in me...
她们不能见到心中魔女...